<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Tips>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        If you find bugs or have an idea for a new feature, file an issue on Trac

        http://trac.osgeo.org/mapguide

        Please be a descriptive as possible when filing issues. For bugs, a 
        step-by-step process of reproducing the bug is very helpful.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Drag and drop a MapGuide package file into the Site Explorer to load it

        Similarly, drag and drop a SDF, SHP or SQLite file to create a
        Feature Source of the same type.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        The Edit as XML toolbar command allows you to edit the XML content of any
        open resource.

        Once complete, the open editor will be re-initialized with the latest
        XML content.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Resource validation can detect and diagnose many common MapGuide problems.

        To validate a resource, right click it in the Site Explorer and choose 
        "Validate"
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        The Site Explorer supports multiple selection. You can now copy/move/validate
        multiple selected resources at once!
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Have a lot of custom commands in your Web Layout?

        You can use the Import/Export functionality in the Web Layout editor to copy
        and move these commands between web layouts.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        If Maestro cannot find a specialized editor that supports the resource you 
        want to open, it will use the XML editor as a fallback option.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        The New Resource dialog supports custom user resource templates.

        Simply drop your XML file into the User Template directory and the New Resource
        dialog will load this template under the "User Defined" category.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Items in the Site Explorer are colored based on whether they are open and/or
        have been edited.
        
        You can configure these colors in the Maestro options.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        The Local Feature Source Preview tool is a powerful way to inspect the data
        and structure of any Feature Source. 
        
        This tool is accessible from the Tools menu and also the Feature Source 
        editor.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        MgCooker is a utility to pre-generate tiles, resulting in faster tiled maps.

        This tool is accessible from the Tools menu and also the Map Definition
        editor.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        If you want to use Google/Bing/Yahoo maps with Fusion, your Map Definition
        needs to be in the Popular Visualisation Mercator coordinate system. 
        
        The coordinate system code for this is WGS84.PseudoMercator
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        If you want to use Google/Bing/Yahoo maps with Fusion, Google and Yahoo maps
        require API keys. Bing does not require API keys. 
        
        Please carefully read the terms and conditions of each respective mapping 
        provider.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Previews of Symbols from a Symbol Library in the Layer Definition editor will 
        currently only show the Symbol as-is. It won't take into account the size and 
        color override settings of your point rule.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Want to know what's new in this release? Check out the changelog.txt in the
        Maestro installation directory.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Check out the author's blog for other MapGuide, Maestro and FDO tips and tricks.
        
        http://themapguyde.blogspot.com
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Do you find Maestro very useful for you? Consider making a Paypal donation to
        the author. 
        
        The donation link is in the about dialog under: Help - About
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        The coordinate system picker allows fast coordinate system lookup by code, WKT 
        and EPSG number.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        The repointer context command allows you to redirect all current references 
        to the selected resource to reference another resource of your choice.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        You can clear any cached feature source schema information by right-clicking
        the feature source in the Site Explorer and selecting the 
        "Purge Cached Schema Information" context menu command.
    </TipOfTheDay>
    <TipOfTheDay>
        Maestro only supports a sub-set of Load Procedures. Maestro does not support 
        the following Load Procedure types:
        
         - DWG Load Procedure type and any of its associated options
         - Raster Load Procedure type and any of its associated options
         - Convert to SDF option (SDF/SHP Load Procedures)
         - Generalization of data
         - SDF2 to SDF3 conversion
    </TipOfTheDay>
</Tips>